William Leondike

Orlando, Florida, United States



linkedin.com/in/williamleondike



billyleondike@gmail.com



https://github.com/WLeondike



+1(386)405-4144

Summary

While graduating with a certificate in full stack development from the University of Central Florida, I've always been passionate about the code I write. Taking the skills I've learned in JavaScript, CSS, HTML, and Node.js to further expand my abilities as a programmer to bring the user a product that's built with care and dedication. My exceptional ability to organize and analyze will continue to develop with me as I sharpen my programming skills as a full-stack developer each day. I plan to help shape the user experience over the internet, one smile at a time.

Experience



Server

World of Beer Franchising, Inc.

Apr 2019 - Mar 2020 (1 year)

Challenged in a fast-paced environment while delivering fast and efficient service to my customers.

Truck Driver

All My Sons Moving & Storage

Jun 2018 - Feb 2019 (9 months)

Led a team of movers to deliver fast and efficient results for our customers.

Education



University of Central Florida

Continuing Education, Coding 2020 - 2020



Daytona State College

Associate's Degree 2012 - 2016 **General Education**

Skills

Analytical Skills • Adaptability • Continuing Education • Project Management • Time Management • Resource Management